http://sunilkhullar.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy pertains to the Website www.sunilkhullar.com owned by Sunil Khullar InfoTech / Bookkeeping.
Introduction:
Sunil Khullar InfoTech / Bookkeeping undertakes a commitment that it will safeguard the privacy of the visitors to its Website www.sunilkhullar.com.
By using our Website www.sunilkhullar.com, the visitor agrees to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy and also provides consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Effective Date:
This Privacy Policy (‘Policy’) is effective from October 01, 2016. Any existing or prior Privacy Policy stands superseded by it.
Applicability:
This Privacy Policy applies to all data of the visitor(s) to the Website www.sunilkhullar.com collected by by Sunil Khullar InfoTech / Bookkeeping or its subsidiaries or affiliates, etc.
Objective of Privacy Policy:
The objective of this Privacy Policy is to inform all visitor(s) to the Website www.sunilkhullar.com  regarding the use, storage and exchange of information with the visitor(s).
Cookies:
Sunil Khullar InfoTech / Bookkeeping may use cookies. The purpose of cookies is to identify the visitors to its Website www.sunilkhullar.com. By viewing Website www.sunilkhullar.com, the visitor(s) agree to and accept the use of cookies by Sunil Khullar InfoTech / Bookkeeping as stated herein.
Collection of Information:
Information collected of the visitor(s) to its Website www.sunilkhullar.com by Sunil Khullar InfoTech / Bookkeeping may include details regarding the IP address, time period of visit, page(s) viewed, date and time of visit, geographical location, browser, operating system, Website navigation paths, personal details, choices and preferences, email ID, information revealed while availing services through the Website or in communication with us, etc.
Use of Information:
The visitor to the Website www.sunilkhullar.com consents to  Sunil Khullar InfoTech / Bookkeeping using information collected for data collection purposes, preparing customer analysis, making any amendment to the Website or in such other manner as deemed fit by Sunil Khullar InfoTech / Bookkeeping. The information collected may be communicated with third parties by Sunil Khullar InfoTech / Bookkeeping.
Transfer of Data:
The visitor to the Website www.sunilkhullar.com consents to the transfer of data globally by Sunil Khullar InfoTech / Bookkeeping in a manner as deemed fit by it at its discretion.
Security of Information:
Sunil Khullar InfoTech / Bookkeeping will  take reasonable steps to ensure the security of information revealed by visitor(s) on its Website www.sunilkhullar.com. Visitor(s) are advised not to reveal any confidential or personal information while visiting the Website www.sunilkhullar.com.
Sunil Khullar InfoTech / Bookkeeping is not responsible for any breach of security or for the actions of the third parties with whom it shares information.
Disclosure of information:
Sunil Khullar InfoTech / Bookkeeping may disclose information collected of the visitor(s) to its Website www.sunilkhullar.com to law enforcement agencies or to any of our employees, officers, insurers, professional advisers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors and others insofar as reasonably necessary for the purpose(s) set out in this Privacy Policy.
Transfer of Information:
Any visitor(s) obtaining information from the Website www.sunilkhullar.com undertakes and consents to provide the same level of data protection and privacy as the Website www.sunilkhullar.com provides to its visitor(s).
Grievance Redressal:
Any grievance or complaint related to this Privacy Policy may be communicated to the email ID:
info@sunilkhullar.com
The grievance or complaint shall be redressed as expeditiously as possible.
Change in Privacy Policy:
This Privacy Policy may be changed at any time with or without notice by Sunil Khullar InfoTech / Bookkeeping at its sole discretion and the same shall be effective.
Legal:
All disputes shall be subject to exclusive jurisdiction of the Courts of Mandi Gobindgarh, Punjab, India and subject to the laws of the State of Punjab, India.
Limitation of Liability:
Liability of Sunil Khullar InfoTech / Bookkeeping with respect to this Privacy Policy will be restricted to Re. 1 (Rupee one).
We are the qualified team of Intuit Pro-Advisors at Sunil Khullar InfoTech. All our team members are certified QuickBooks consultant, competent enough to handle recording your business financial transactions in  compliance with US structure. We are the well-equipped professionals with advanced QuickBooks product knowledge with years of experience to bring the best result to your table.
We, the Sunil Khullar InfoTech’s Intuit Pro-Advisors, help big and small business owners and their accountants. Further, we also cater CPAs, accounting firms and companies in getting the most out of QuickBooks. Read more
Click Here to see our Profile on Intuit ProAdvisor Website
Sunil Khullar InfoTech / Bookkeeping
+1-(904)-256-9053
info@sunilkhullar.com
